<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Installations on free5GC</title>
    <link>https://free5gc.org/installations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Installations on free5GC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://free5gc.org/installations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-1-all-in-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-1-all-in-one/</guid>
      <description>free5GC Installation on KVM Minimum Requirement   Software
 OS: Ubuntu 18.04 Linux kernel: 4.15.0-43-generic gcc 7.3.0 Go 1.11.4 QEMU emulator 2.11.1    Hardware
 CPU: Intel i5 processor RAM: 4GB Hard drive: 160G NIC card: 1Gbps ethernet card    Hardware recommended
 CPU: Intel i7 processor RAM: 8GB Hard drive: 160G NIC card: 10Gbps ethernet card    Hardware Tested eNB</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-1-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-1-cluster/</guid>
      <description>free5GC Distributed Installation Guide Network Topology  Install free5GC About MongoDB  MongoDB MUST be installed on the HSS machine in distributed installation and make sure all entities are accessing to the that database. Please add UE infomation to webUI on the HSS machine. Please modify the MongoDB address (at the first line of free5gc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-2-standalone-5g/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-2-standalone-5g/</guid>
      <description>free5GC Stage 2 Installation Guide Minimum Requirement  Software  OS: Ubuntu 18.04 or later versions gcc 7.3.0 Go 1.12.9 linux/amd64 QEMU emulator 2.11.1    Note: Please use Ubuntu 18.04 or later versions and go 1.12.9 linux/amd64
You can use go version to check your current Go version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-appendix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-appendix/</guid>
      <description>Appendix A: OAM  Run the OAM server  cd webconsole go run server.go Access the OAM by  URL: http://localhost:5000 Username: admin Password: free5gc Now you can see the information of currently registered UEs (e.g. Supi, connected state, etc.) in the core network at the tab &amp;ldquo;DASHBOARD&amp;rdquo; of free5GC webconsole  Note: You can add the subscribers here too</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-configuration/</guid>
      <description>SBI Configuration There are registerIP and bindingIP design on every NF&amp;rsquo;s sbi interface.
This is due to some orchestration, such as Kubernets or OpenStack, has the design of service IP mapping.
Use Kubernets as an example. K8S has the service type that enable users to define the service IP outside the pod.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-demo-tw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-demo-tw/</guid>
      <description>free5GC Stage 3 安裝示範 此示範分兩階段。第一部分我們將：
 安裝 VirtualBox 在 VirtualBox 上安裝 Ubuntu Server VM (虛擬機器) 在本機藉由 SSH 連線到 Ubuntu 並安裝 free5GC stage 3 執行 free5GC 的測試腳本  第二部分我們將：
 建立第二個 Ubuntu Server VM 藉由 SSH, install a third-party UE and RAN emulator on the VM 藉由 SSH 連線到此 VM， 安裝一開源 UE 及 RAN 的模擬器 (UERANSIM) 啟動 free5GC 5G 核網，並使用此模擬器經由核網連線至網際網路  1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-demo/</guid>
      <description>free5GC Stage 3 Installation Demo In the first part of the demo, we will
 install VirtualBox create a Ubuntu Server VM using VirtualBox use SSH to connect to the Ubuntu VM to install free5GC stage 3 run free5GC test scripts  In the second part, we will
 create another Ubuntu Server VM via SSH, install a third-party UE and RAN emulator on the VM use the emulator to access Internet through the free5GC core network  1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-environment/</guid>
      <description>Recommended Environment free5gc has been tested against the following environment:
 Software  OS: Ubuntu 18.04 gcc 7.3.0 Go 1.14.4 linux/amd64 kernel version 5.0.0-23-generic    The listed kernel version is required for the UPF element.
  Minimum Hardware
 CPU: Intel i5 processor RAM: 4GB Hard drive: 160GB NIC: Any 1Gbps Ethernet card supported in the Linux kernel    Recommended Hardware</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-free5gc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-free5gc/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Hardware Tested Detail information Questions Recommended Environment Installation  A. Prerequisites B. Install User Plane Function (UPF) C. Install Control Plane Elements   Run  A. Run the Core Network B. Run the N3IWF (Individually) C. Run all-in-one with outside RAN D. Deploy within containers   Test Release Note  Hardware Tested In the market today, there are neither hardware gNB nor hardware UEs that interface directly with a standalone 5GC, so no hardware testing has yet been performed against free5gc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-installation/</guid>
      <description>Installation A. Prerequisites   Linux Kernel Version
 In order to use the UPF element, you must use the 5.0.0-23-generic version of the Linux kernel. free5gc uses the gtp5g kernel module, which has been tested and compiled against that kernel version only. To determine the version of the Linux kernel you are using:  $ uname -r 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-old/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-old/</guid>
      <description>  free5GC Stage 3 Installation Guide For installation, please check:
 Environment Installation A Step-by-step Installation Example (中文版)  For how to configure, check on:
 Configuration SMF  For Running free5GC, check:
 Testing free5GC Running free5GC free5GC Compose  Others
 Trouble Shooting Appendix  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-run/</guid>
      <description>Run A. Run the Core Network Option 1. Run network function services individually. For example, to run the AMF:
cd ~/free5gc ./bin/amf Note: The N3IWF needs specific configuration, which is detailed in section B.
Option 2. Run whole core network
cd ~/free5gc ./run.sh B. Run the N3IWF (Individually) To run an instance of the N3IWF, make sure your system is equipped with three network interfaces: the first connects to the AMF, the second connects to the UPF, and the third is for IKE daemon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-smf-config/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-smf-config/</guid>
      <description>SMF Config / ULCL Config This document explains the detail of SMF config. Also provide some examples about conversion between config file and real userplane topology
ULCL limitation: The branching UPF now can&amp;rsquo;t connect to the Internet. It only serves as a Intranet in the UPF topology. (Please refers to the topology of example 2)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-test/</guid>
      <description>Test Start a Wireshark capture on any core-connected interface, applying the filter &#39;pfcp||icmp||gtp&#39;.
In order to run the tests, first do this:
cd ~/free5gc chmod +x ./test.sh The tests are all run from within ~/free5gc.
a. TestRegistration
./test.sh TestRegistration b. TestGUTIRegistration
./test.sh TestGUTIRegistration c. TestServiceRequest
./test.sh TestServiceRequest d. TestXnHandover
./test.sh TestXnHandover e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-trouble-shooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-trouble-shooting/</guid>
      <description>Trouble Shooting 1. ERROR: [SCTP] Failed to connect given AMF N3IWF=NGAP This error occured when N3IWF was started before AMF finishing initialization. This error usually appears when you run the TestNon3GPP in the first time.
Rerun the test should be fine. If it still not be solved, larger the sleeping time in line 110 of test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-vm-basics-tw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-vm-basics-tw/</guid>
      <description>Ubuntu 虛擬機器安裝示範 此示範我們將：
 安裝 VirtualBox 在 VirtualBox 上安裝 Ubuntu Server VM (虛擬機器) 在本機藉由 SSH 連線到 Ubuntu 並安裝 free5GC stage 3  1. 安裝 VirtualBox 開啟瀏覽器搜尋 &amp;ldquo;virtualbox download&amp;quot;， 到 VirtualBox 官網 virtualbox.org 下載並安裝最新 VirtualBox. (例如本文撰寫當下為 6.1.6 版本)
VirtualBox 官網 https://virtualbox.org  安裝成功後，試著打開 VirtualBox 看是否有類似下圖之視窗 (下圖為 Mac 版本)：
 2. 下載最新 Ubuntu Server LTS 搜尋 &amp;ldquo;ubuntu server download&amp;quot;，到 Ubuntu 官網 下載最新 Ubuntu Server LTS 的 .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-vm-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3-vm-basics/</guid>
      <description>Ubuntu Virtual Machine Installation Demo In this demo, we will
 install VirtualBox create a Ubuntu Server VM using VirtualBox use SSH to connect to the Ubuntu VM to install free5GC stage 3  1. Install VirtualBox   search &amp;ldquo;virtualbox download&amp;rdquo;, or visit virtualbox.org to download and install VirtualBox (currently 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free5gc.org/installations/stage-3/</guid>
      <description>  free5GC Stage 3 Installation Guide For information about installation and configuration of the latest free5GC, please visit
 free5GC Documentation  For people who are not familiar with virtual machine and Linux installation, here are some example instructions:
 Creating a Ubuntu VM using VirtualBox (Chinese Version)  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
